Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - Head, Glenn, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Huberman, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Hunter, Christian, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Indiana, Gary, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Isaac, Jeffrey a.k.a. Zagreus Bowery, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - James, Darius, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Jankowski, Matty, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Joyce, W, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Kasper, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Kaz, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - King, J.D., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Kolm, Ron ("In a word"), undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Kruger, Barbara, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kruth, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - LaBombarda, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Litzsky, Tsaurah, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Lopatin, Judy, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - McCall, Bruce, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - McGlyn, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - McGrath, Patrick, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Madore, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Mandl, Dave, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Mathews, Harry, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Maynard, Joe, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Mazzucchelli, D, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Miller, Stephen Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Moisan, Jim, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Moriarty, J, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Olsen, Lance, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Ostashevsky, Eugene (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Otterness, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Padua, Jose, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Panter, G, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Passaro, Vince, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Pincus, Harry, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Potash, Chris, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Randall, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Rankin, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Rattray, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Rosen, Jonathan, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Rower, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Sandlin, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Savage, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Sedaris, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Sendak, Maurice, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Shalom (full, legal name: Shalom Newman), undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sipes, Steven, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sparrow (legal name: Michael Gorelick), undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sparrow, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Strausbaugh, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Texier, Catherine, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ulin, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Walker, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Watson, Carl, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Watson, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Weiss, Thomas, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Wilson, Blair, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, Peter Lamborn (aka Hakim Bey), undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Witz, Bob, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Wodizcko, Krysztof, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Yourgrau, Barry, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Zummer, Thomas, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    This subseries contains materials about subjects in the downtown scene, like stamp art, vend art, etc. It also contains items documenting Ron Kolm's career working for independent bookstores.
    - Berserker Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Between C & D Anthology, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Between C & D Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Bookstores, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Book Zine Web Fair, Cafe Nico, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Business Cards, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Cartoon, exhibitions, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Cartoonists, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - City Lights, Booksellers & Publishers, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - East Village Culture, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Fact Sheet Five Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Fiction Collective 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Films, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Fusion Arts Books, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Graffiti, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Hallwalls, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Handelines, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Hard Press Poetry Postcards, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Hoboken Terminal Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Instant Classics, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Katonah -- Zummer materials, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Limited Time Only Magazine, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Local Boy Makes Good--Appearances #21, Mike Topp Issue, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Low Tech Press, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Madame Rosa's, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Magazines, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous Art File, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Mondo Barbie, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Music, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - National Poetry Magazine Of The Lower East Side, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Neoism -- Correspondence Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - New Leaves Review, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New Morning Bookstore, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Panic Button Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Pinched Nerves, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Poetry Project, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Poet's House (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Portable Lower East Side, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Public Illuminations Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Rant Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - RAW, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Reviews - Subyear Files (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Rubber Stamps, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop -- Letter File, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Seven Deadly Sins, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Single Cell Show--Katonah Art Museum/Gallery, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Smoke Signals, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Soho Arts Weekly (SAW), undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Southpaw Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Technoscience & Cyberculture--Peter Lamborn Wilson, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Test Drive (Appearances #22), undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Vend Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Ward Nasse Gallery, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Wexner & Katonah, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - WFMU 91.1 Radio Station, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Writer's Market, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Zone Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Series V: Photographs
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables
    This subseries consists of one small box of photographs, mostly of The Unbearables.
    - Whole Heart by Shalom (Shelved in oversize), undated (Binder 69)
    - Sparrow For President photo, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photo of Denise Duhamel, undated (Binder 69)
    - Merry Christmas photo of Richard Peabody, undated (Binder 69)
    - 3 photos from the "Low Tech Manual" reading, 1981 Participant: Ron Kolm (Binder 69)
    - Photo of "Assissi" with the name "Jeffrey Isaac" on back, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photo of Thomas Zummer & Leslie Thornton filming "The Great Invisible", undated (Binder 69)
    - Production still of "The Great Invisible" with Thomas Zummer and others, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photo of "Isabelle Eberhardt and her mother, Natalie de Moerder" from "The Great Invisible", undated (Binder 69)
    - 20 color photos of "Unbearables" at Shandon Star 9/25/96. Participants: Ron Kolm, Joe Maynard, Bob McGlyn, Susan Scutti, Bonnie Finberg, Liz Resko, Bart Plantenga, Mike Golden, Dave Mandl, Michael Randall, Hal Sirowitz, Tsaurah Litzky, Lorraine Schein, 1996 (Binder 69)
    - 2 Photos of Joe Lewis, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photo of unidentified woman, undated (Binder 69)
    - Two sheets of old, photo booth pictures taken at Bleecker St. Bar, 1990? Participants: Ron Kolm, Jose Padua, Ralph Ackerman, Mike Golden, Carol Wierzbicki (Binder 69)
    - A Large, black & white photo of Unbearables for the Village Voice (oversized). Participants: Bob Witz (standing) Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Michael Carter, Alfred Vitale, Jim Feast (seated), undated (Binder 69)
    - B Small, black & white photo of Unbearables for the Village Voice. Participants: Bob Witz, Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Alfred Vitale, Jim Feast, Michael Carter, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photos --33 photos from the Memory City Reading. Participants: Ron Kolm, Carl Watson, Jim Feast, Bob Witz, Hal Sirowitz, Carol Wierbicki, Bart Plantenga, Alfred Vitale, Michael Carter, Jill Rapaport, Rob Hardin, Joe Maynard, David Huberman, Christian X. Hunter, Bonnie Finberg, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photos -- 28 photos from a Rant Benefit Reading. Participants: Jim Feast, Alfred Vitale, Susan Scutti, Ron Kolm, Tsaurah Litzsky, Joe Maynard, Dave Mandl, Bart Plantenga, Michael Carter, Carol Wierzbicki, and others, undated (Binder 69)
    - Large photo of the Saint Mark's Bookshop at it's old location (oversized), undated (Binder 69)
    - 2 color photos of paintings by Michael Randall, undated (Binder 69)
    - 2 Photos of Bob Witz with his paintings, undated (Binder 69)
    - 1 small "Kodalux" box of slides. Contents: 6 slides by William Anthony illustrating Ron Kolm's work, undated (Binder 69)
    - 1 sheet of slides "Voices of Aftershock", undated (Binder 69)
    - Miscellaneous photos of "Unbearables", undated (Binder 69)
    - 1 black & white photo of Michael Randall painting, 1 slide. (Both in envelope with the words: "Michael Randall painting that became cover for Kolm's Plastic Fact."), undated (Binder 69)
    - 21 Photos from Second New Yorker Protest. Participants: Ron Kolm, Alfred Vitale, Tom Savage,Jim Feast, Bart Plantenga, Joe Maynard, Sparrow, Carol Wierzbicki, Bob Witz, Jill Rapaport, Michael Carter, Lorraine Schein, Shalom, Michael Carter, Lawrence Fishberg, Lorraine Schein, William Anthony, & others, undated (Binder 69)
    - 5 Photos from a Reading on the Brooklyn Bridge. Participants: Peter Lamborn Wilson, Tom Savage, Dave Mandl, Jim Feast, Bart Plantenga, Bruce Weber, David Huberman, Sparrow, Ron Kolm, Alfred Vitale, and others, undated (Binder 69)
    - Photo of a painting by Patrick Stevenson, undated (Binder 69)
    - 19 photos of Unbearables at Armstrong's Bar for Cups Magazine May 31, 1996. Participants: Ron Kolm, Sharon Mesmer, Jim Feast, Marvin Taylor, Janice Eidus, Mike Topp, Alexander Lawrence (Binder 69)
  - Subseries B: Coliseum Books Photographs
    This subseries consists of one binder of pictures from throughout Ron Kolm's tenure at Coliseum Books.
    - Coliseum Bookstore Christmas Party, 1990s (Binder 70)
    - Darwin Hageman and John Underwood (Binder 70)
    - Pam Carter, 2001 (Binder 70)
    - Corey Groom, 2001 (Binder 70)
    - Michael Audas and Ronald Stephenson, 2001 (Binder 70)
    - Lino Azevedo, 2001 (Binder 70)
    - Annie (Binder 70)
    - Weber Jenson (Binder 70)
    - Kevin and Jefferson (Binder 70)
    - Staff at McCoy's, 2000 (Binder 70)
    - Store Christmas Party, 2000 (Binder 70)
    - Lino as Elvis/Closing Party, 2002 (Binder 70)
    - Area Excavated for Store Elevator, 1994 (Binder 70)
- Series VI: Announcements
  This series contains nnouncements for readings, gallery shows, and other events.
  - Subseries A: Readings
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by venue.
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Alchemical Theater, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Anseo, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Attitude Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Back Fence, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Bernard & Steve's, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Biblio's, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Blue Mountain, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - B.O.B, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Bookstore Readings, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Brecht Forum, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - CBGB, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Cedar Tavern, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Chez Rollo, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Cold Fish, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Darinka, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - DIA Center For The Arts, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Dixon Place, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Ear Inn, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Exit Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Fez Under Time Cafe, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - The Garden (6th St.& Ave. B), undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - The Gas Station, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Granary Books, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Hearn Gallery, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Image Theater, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - The Kitchen, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - The Knitting Factory, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - La Mama Galleria, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Life Cafe, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Limelight, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - The Living Theater, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - The Medicine Show, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Neither/Nor, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - New York Public Library, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Cafe Nico, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Cafe No Bar, undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Nuyorican Poets Cafe, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Palsson's Restaurant, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - P.S. 122, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Duplicates, undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Poemfone, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - The Poetry Project, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - The Pyramid Club, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Segue Foundation Performance Space, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Skep, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Speak Easy, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Spiral Bar, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - The Thread Waxing Space, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Up Front Muse, undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Ward Nasse Gallery, undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Group Readings, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reading Announcements, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Performances (Non-Readings), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Bruce Benderson, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Readings-- David Rattray, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Readings -- Hal Sirowitz, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Readings--Barry Yourgrau, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Readings -- Max Blagg, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Announcements -- Plays, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Book Parties/Publication Announcements, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Calendars 1981--1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Poetry Calendars 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Poetry Calendars 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Poetry Calendars 1991--1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Poetry Calendars 1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by gallery or by artist.
    - ABC No Rio, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Adams, Jeff, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - ala Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Vikki, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Andrucyk, Inez, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Anthony, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Armijo, Richard, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Artist's Space, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Baer Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Baxter, Glen, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Blachy, Jimbo, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bluhm, Norman, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Bordo, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Burkhart, Kathe, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Ken, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - C., Jim, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Capp Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - CB's 313 Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Clemente, Francesco, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Coe, Sue, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Collins & Millazzo Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Costan, Chris, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Crumb, R, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Dali, Salvador, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Drooker, Eric, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Ecker, Ken, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Exit Art, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Fachetti Galleries, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Fine, Larry, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Finley, Karen, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Folzenlogen, Tim, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Gosfield, Josh, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Grooms, Red, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Gross, Mimi, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Hamburger, Sydney, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Helio Galleries, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Heller, Neddi, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Holness, Victor, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Isaac, Jeffrey, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Jensen, Bill, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Jernigan, Candy, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Kaufman, Betsy, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kruth, John, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Madore, Michael, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Malanga, Gerard, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Miller, John, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Ochiishi, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Palaia, Franc, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Public Illumination Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Raveson, Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Sandlin, David, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Sharpe Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Sides, Wayne, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Stevenson, Patrick, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Tompkins, Betty, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Turyn, Anne, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ward-Nasse Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - White Columns Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Blair, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Witz, Robert, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Zelevansky, Paul, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Announcements, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Group Shows, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Series VII: Sound recordings
  This series consists of sound recordings and video recordings on various formats, and includes poetry, music, and spoken word recordings.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Anthony, Bill -- Slide Show. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Batteries Not Included. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Best Wishes To Rank. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max--Five Days, (Fez), 4/21/93. Audiotape Cassette, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max -- Monkey Wrench, etc., The Other Gallery, 2/1/90 Audiotape Cassette, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Blagg, Max -- 10/28/87. Audiotape Cassette, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Cherches, Peter -- Sonorexia, w/ Elliott Sharpe & others. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Cherches, Peter -- Videotape, w/ Lee Feldman 11/7/86, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence -- 10 Songs in only a little over 15 minutes, 1995. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Fugs, The -- Keeping The Issues Alive, Ed Sanders, Tuli Kupferberg, others 1984. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - In-Cafe Cool -- Cups. Loudon Wainright, others n.d. Compact Disc, undated (Box 29)
  - Just Say Ho -- audiotape cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Holman, Bob -- Panic DJ. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron - 11/15/86. Audiotape Cassette, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Nuyorican Poets Cafe 3/24/90. Audiotape Cassette, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Ridge St. Gallery Reading, w/Hal Sirowitz 11/14/87. Audiotape Cassette, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Songs (by Fishberg,) 1995. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Swimming At The Shallow End Of The Pool, 1995 (2 copies) Audiotape Cassettes (Box 29)
  - Kruth, John -- Midnight Snack. Compact Disc, undated (Box 29)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli -- Seance Piece. "Tuli Channels Marx" 3/29/94 Audiotape Cassette, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli -- Tuli & Friends. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Mellow Freakin' Woodies-- Mellow Freakin' Mood. 1992. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Merry Christmas The North Pole Bull Shit, 1986 (?) Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Nuyorican Symphony -- 100 poets including. Bob Holman, Carolyn Peyser, Eileen Myles, Carl Watson, Edwin Torres, Miguel Algarin, Ron Kolm, Sparrow, Sapphire, etc. 1992, Compact Disc (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart - Avec "After he vomited, Bart sat on a rock." Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Greetings From Home Of Freedom. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Mr. Valbar May Just Have Won Five Million Dollars - Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Poetry As Healer. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Word Is The Bird. AH - OOO. Sperm motility, etc. Audiotape Cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Silent Not -- audiotape cassette & tattoo, undated (Box 29)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- Idiodyssey, 1993. w/Lawrence Fishberg. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Sparrow -- May I Take A Bath, (Foamola), 1992. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Sparrow -- Spit On The Dishes (Foamola), 1993. Audiotape Cassette (Box 29)
  - Unbearables At Fales -- NYU 5/7/96. Videotape, 1996 (Box 29)
  - Unbearable Beatniks Of Life --The Poetry Project, 2/22/93 Tape 1: Max Blagg, Michael Carter, Jim Feast, David Ulin, Jill Rapaport, Ron Kolm, Sharon Mesmer, Bart Plantenga Audiotape Cassette, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Unbearable Beatniks Of Life -- The Poetry Project 2/22/93 Tape 2: Bart Plantenga, Jim Feast, Deborah Pintonelli, Hal Sirowitz, Jill Rapaport. Audiotape Cassette, 1993 (Box 29)
  - What Makes A Poem Great? --audiotape cassette, undated (Box 29)
  - Wild Words -- Cups Records. William Burroughs, Hal Sirowitz, Charles Bukowski, Harvey Fierstein, Paul Bowles, Hakim Bey (a.k.a. Peter Lamborn Wilson), Bob Holman, and others. Compact Disc, undated (Box 29)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn -- T.A.Z. Hakim Bey. Compact Disc, undated (Box 29)
- Series VIII: Original Art
  This series contains a small collection of original art works by downtown artists.
  - Adams, Jeffrey--3 originals for "Back Fence" readings, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)